您的账单
Here's your check.
薯条没算在里面 因为被我吃掉了
I didn't charge you for the fries, 'cause I ate them.
Max 当心!
Max, look out!
餐厅里的水蝽大得惊人
The diner water bugs are getting really big.
别紧张 这是餐厅最新的无人侦察机
Relax, it's the diner's new surveillance drone.
天啊 我只是中饱私囊了几次
God, you empty the register five or ten times,
转眼信任就没了
suddenly there's no trust.
所以我们连肥皂都没有 却有架无人机?
So to be clear, we're out of soap but we have a drone?
我真受不了Han在暗地里监控我们
I hate that Han's just sitting in back, watching us,
还把操纵杆玩得那么欢
working his little joy stick.
拜托 就Han那小棒棒任谁也欢不了
Please, no one's getting any joy out of Han's little stick.
这家伙真烦人
This is so annoying.
总跟我屁股后面
It's following me.
就你那扁平的屁股 这是唯一一个
Well, with a butt that flat, it's the only black thing
肯跟在你身后的黑大壮了吧
that's ever going to follow you.
这里还有只嗡嗡叫的家伙?
Ugh, there's another drone out here?
我刚在厨房用苍蝇拍拍死一只
I just killed one in the kitchen with a fly swatter.
走开
Go.
我要是想被暗中监视
I mean, if I wanted to be spied on,
早就改名叫阿克曼了
I'd change my name to Achmed,
"往生恐怖份子阿克曼"是网络点击率极高的表演短片
或者是在机场附件买个公寓
and buy a condo near the airport.
咋不买这样的一幅画呢
Whatever happened to buying a painting
画着一个老船长把观察孔挖空
of an old sea captain, drilling out the eye holes,
躲在后面窥视的那种
and hiding behind it?
这样不好 Han
Not cool, Han.
最糟糕的是 它老是乱动
And the worst part is, it's moving around so much,
害得我都找不准角度
I can't find my good angle.
这样就不是Han的做派了
Not cool and not Han.
这是在他跟我解释拿最低工资的
I stole this while he was explaining to me
77岁老头为何不需要医保的时候
why a 77-year-old man, on minimum wage,
我趁机偷的
doesn't need health care.
Earl 这挺不错的啊
Earl, that is awesome.
才不好 我真的需要那医保
Not really. I need that health care.
不 我指的是你偷的这玩意
No, that you stole that.
我们得采取点措施 好让Han
We need to do something that will make Han
永远不再想监视我们
never want to spy on us again.
Oleg 解开裤带
Oleg, open your pants.
Earl 把摄像头对准那里
Earl, fly that camera in there.
但首先 你得脱掉内裤
But first, take off your underwear.
内裤?
Underwear?
别逗了 当我还小?
Come on. What am I, five?
还是我"弟弟"小?
Inches?
Oleg 你难道不担心Earl的白内障吗?
Oleg, aren't you at all worried about Earl's cataracts?
最好的打算 是被刮掉阴毛
Best case scenario, I get a little manscaping.
最差的打算 就是被割下包皮
Worst case, I've been meaning to get circumcised.
我被亮瞎了!
My eyes!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴: 奥利奥
翻译: 奥利奥  落寞卷菜  初见  morning
校对: 桃茜茜
Max 我在填写银行贷款的支票
Max, I'm writing out the check for our bank loan,
但不是很确定余额是多少
and I'm not quite sure what our balance is
因为在"提款"处 你只写了"是的"
because here under "Withdrawal"" You just wrote, "Yeah""
你不喜欢那个的话 肯定也不会喜欢
Well, if you don't like that, you're really not going to like
我在"存款"处作的画了
the picture I drew under "Deposits."
我看见了
I saw it.
Max 零可不是蛋蛋 不是咪咪
Max, zeroes are not balls, they're not boobs,
更不是金鱼眼
and they're not googly eyes.
零就只是零
They're just zeroes.
那是你认为
Says you.
我去取款机查查余额
I'll go check our balance at the ATM.
虽然刚刚使用这机器的人
Even though the last guy who touched it
长了个很大的唇疱疹
had a cold sore so big,
我收了他两倍的费用
I charged him for a party of two.
别担心 你从那台破机器上
Don't worry. You are not going to get anything
什么都得不到
from that machine.
特别是钱
Especially cash.
嗨 各位亲
Hey, everybody.
对了
Oh, yeah.
来个人给我煮些蛋蛋
Somebody better make me some eggs
因为我进行了三个小时的果汁节食
because I've been on a juice cleanse for three hours,
都饿晕了
and I'm dizzy.
他们说这种方法很有效
Yeah. I mean, they call it a fast,
但很显然见效慢
but it sure does go slow.
曾有人说很快 结果我等了三个星期
I was on a three weeks fast, once.
然后我才意识到我妈不会回家了
Then I realized my mother wasn't coming home.
所以我自己做了个三明治
So I made a sandwich.
我和Oleg新婚在即
Oleg and my wedding is coming up
我们想吃得干净一点
and we're trying to eat clean.
没错 宝贝 因为我们度蜜月时
Yeah, baby, 'cause you know we're eating dirty
会吃那些淫水
on the honeymoon.
老天爷啊 怎么了?
Oh, dear God, what?
收据槽里又塞了个套套?
Another used condom in the receipt slot?
- 比这更糟  - 那是什么?
- Worse.   - What?
该戴套套却没有戴?
Stuff that should be in a condom but isn't?
我们负债了
We're below zero.
我得走了 伙计们
Oh, well, I better go, y'all.
有个白人妇女在我身边尖叫
A white woman screaming anywhere in my vicinity
绝对不是好事
never turns out well.
这简直是飞来横祸
This is a disaster.
我曾经一无所有过
I've been at zero,
但从不至于亏空
but I've never had less than zero.
别这么说 Caroline
Oh, don't say that, Caroline.
你忘了你的约会对象人数了
I mean, you're forgetting about your dating options.
我们现在负债了
We have less than zero money
无法偿还银行贷款
and no way of paying off our bank loan.
天啊 终于落到这地步了
Oh, my God. It happened.
我成工人阶级了
I'm working class.
嘿 我跟你一块儿当了四年的服务员
Hey. I've waited tables with you for four years
你敢说自己这是在工作吗
and there's no way you could call what you do working.
纸杯蛋糕!
Cupcakes!
买纸杯蛋糕
Buy cupcakes.
来买纸杯蛋糕!
Buy cupcakes!
别喊了
Stop.
你看着比卡尔文广告里的贾斯汀·比伯
You look more desperate than Justin Bieber
还要绝望
in that Calvin Klein ad.
你根本不懂银行贷款的事
You don't understand the seriousness
有多么严重
of this bank situation.
你根本不懂魔兽世界里的规则
You don't understand the rules of World Of Warcraft.
贷款会不断地翻倍增加
The loan just keeps escalating and escalating
直到逼我们倒闭
until they close us down.
纸杯蛋糕! 来买纸杯蛋糕!
Cupcakes! Buy cupcakes!
来买纸杯蛋糕! 来买纸杯蛋糕!
Buy cupcakes! Buy cupcakes!
快看 有肥肉
Oh, Pay-dirt. Look.
是联谊会那又肥又胖的大个子
Here comes a big, fat frat house guy.
嘿 贱人们
Hey, bitches.
还记得我吗?
Remember me?
大个子玛丽
Big Mary.
就是这名字 永不过时
That's my name. Don't wear it out.
John 从糕点学校后就没见过你
John, we haven't seen you since pastry school.
嘿 看在老交情上 要买个纸杯蛋糕吗?
Hey, for old times' sake, want to buy a cupcake?
一打? 整个店?
A dozen? The shop?
我来这里是因为我可能
So I came because I may know of a way
有办法让Max赚一些外快
for Max to make some extra money.
不管什么工作 她都做
Whatever it is, she'll do it.
那可是我纪念册上的座右铭
That was my yearbook quote.
我刚刚入职一家新开的餐厅
I just got hired at a new restaurant
就在曼哈顿的
that's opening under the High Line Park
高线公园 他们正在招聘一名
in Manhattan, and they are looking
白天上班的糕点师
for another day pastry chef.
我虽然只在糕点学校呆了一年
I only have a year of pastry school
不过貌似那一年我都神智恍惚
and I was stoned for, like, a year of that.
我不知道我能不能胜任
I don't know if I have the skills.
噢 别逗了 你肯定不够资格
Oh, girl, you don't.
但是那个经理 Joe 只看脸
But the manager, Joe, wants only pretty people.
你的美貌和性感足以
And what you lack in pastry,
弥补你专业能力的不足
you more than make up for in pretty.
她会去的 你会去的Max
She'll do it. You'll do it, Max.
有技术高超的John在那里
And John will be there to help back you up
他会帮助你的
with his pastry skills.
人家也是很美貌的
And 'cause I'm pretty.
我觉得那种地方不适合我
I don't belong in a place like that.
餐厅的名字叫 "糕潮"
It's called "The High."
听起来不错 地址给我
Sounds right. Give me the deets.
嗨 晚上好 女士们
Well, good night girls.
你们负债了 为此我很难过
Sorry about your bank balance.
但是我相信你们会像从前那样
But I trust you'll both lapse
很快地陷入自我否定当中
into denial fairly soon, as always.
嗨
Hello.
她是谁?
Who was she?
抱紧我 我的小舞伴
Hold me closer, tiny dancer.
噢... Han不是同性恋
Oh... Han's not gay.
仅仅目前 "还不是"
You forgot the "Yet."
Max 是不是应该系上一两个扣子
Max, maybe button up a button or two.
这是餐吧 又不是酒吧
It's a dessert bar. Not a strip bar.
嘿 我需要这份工作
Hey, I need this job,
一旦这个叫Joe的家伙看见这对膨松的大馒头
and once this Joe guy takes one look at these puff pastries,
也许他就会手下留情
he might cut me some slack when he sees
无视我做的那些不怎么膨松的糕点
my other "Not so puff" Pastries.
你这样能心安理得吗?
And you're comfortable with that?
没错
Yup.
就像我觉得
Like I guess you're comfortable
你的服务水平那么差
applying for a waitress job
也敢心安理得地去应聘服务员
on just the merits of your waitress skills.
我要再多解开几个扣子吗?
Should I keep going?
有用吗?
Why?
我来了
I'm here.
把申请表都给我吧 速度 女士们
I'll take those applications. Hurry, ladies.
如果我要找个好看却又反应慢的人 我就会雇佣尼克·乔纳斯
If I was looking for pretty and slow, I'd hire Nick Jonas.
Max 我们走吧
Max, let's get out of here.
她让我想到了
She reminds me of this nightmare
关于自己余生惨状的噩梦
I'm going to have for the rest of my life.
别怕 她只不过是经理的看门狗
Relax, she's just his guard dog.
Joe才是我们要搞定的家伙
It's Joe guy we have to impress.
不行 谢谢
No thank you.
你居然有脸来申请?
And how dare you?
噢 抱歉 明天餐厅才营业呢
Oh, I'm sorry, the restaurant doesn't open until tomorrow.
实际上 不
Actually, no.
嗨 我是来应聘服务生工作的
Hi. I'm here to apply for a waitress job.
就你这把年纪?
At your age?
我27了!
I'm 27!
那又如何?
And?
Max 我不能呼吸了
Max, I can't breathe.
我是来应聘糕点师的
And I'm here to apply for a pastry chef.
我也27 但我从6岁时就长这样
Also 27, but I've looked this old since I was 6.
曾有一段时间 我以为自己都逆生长了
For a while, I thought I had that Benjamin Button's disease.
我先来面试糕点师
I'll take the pastry chef first.
你坐在旁边等会吧
Why don't you sit over there and wait.
不会很久的 因为坦白说
I won't be long, because frankly,
你不会有很多时间的
you don't have the time.
谢谢 我就在那等着
Thank you. I'll be over there.
申请一下社保
Applying for Social Security.
你在哪个学校学的烘焙
So where did you go to pastry school,
现在为什么没工作?
and why aren't you working now?
曼哈顿烘焙学校 我现在有工作
Manhattan School Of Pastry, and I am working.
我在布鲁克林有自己的蛋糕店
I have my own cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
噢 快结束了
Oh, it's almost over.
这次面试? 太棒了
This interview? Great.
不 不是面试 布鲁克林
No. Not the interview. Brooklyn.
布鲁克林快不行了
Brooklyn's almost over.
而且 纸杯蛋糕也没落了
Also, cupcakes.
酷 我会转告他们的
Cool. I will tell them.
真希望我能在他们为了扮酷
Wish I knew that before they all got
在肚脐眼上打孔之前就知道
their belly buttons pierced trying to stay cool.
噢 太棒了 幽默感
Oh, great. A sense of humor.
顾客们喜欢
Customers love that.
我不喜欢 但是他们喜欢
I don't, but they do.
那位叫Joe的帅哥在哪呢?
So, um, where's this Joe guy who's doing the hiring?
这里没有叫Joe的帅哥 我就是Joe
There is no "Joe guy"" I'm Joe.
是这么拼的J-O-E-D-T-H
Spelled, J-O-E-D-T-H.
D-T-H 不发音
The D-T-H is silent.
我也不出声 因为我想要这工作
As am I, because I want this job.
那么 我想我可以把扣子扣上了
Well, I guess I can put these away then.
这就是你的计划?
That was your plan?
袒胸露乳来勾引老板?
To expose your breasts and seduce your way into this job?
听起来你觉得这行为不妥
You say that like it's a bad thing.
那么 好吧 再见
Okay. Well, bye.
且慢 坐下
Sit, sit.
如果你真的能烘焙
If you really can bake,
那么这份工作就很适合你了
this position might be perfect for you.
而且 你很任性
Also, you have that edgy,
一副无所谓的态度
"I don't give a crap" Attitude.
顾客喜欢你这样的
Customers love that.
我不喜欢 但是他们喜欢
I don't, but they do.
其实 DTH不发音的Joe 我会烘焙
Actually, Joe, silent D-T-H, I can bake.
技术怎么样?
But how well?
我女朋友和我对法国糕点很狂热
My girlfriend and I are obsessed with French pastry.
噢 女朋友是真的 "女朋友"
Oh. Girlfriend as in "Girlfriend,"
还是在电影院里
or as in two ladies of a certain age
分吃一桶爆米花的同龄女性朋友?
at a Cineplex splitting one thing of popcorn?
刚刚你说的每一句话都冒犯了我
Everything you just said offended me.
没错 这就是我的特点
Yeah, that's my brand.
而你又没对坐在电影院分吃爆米花
And the fact that you didn't cry
大喊大叫让我觉得
about splitting a popcorn makes me think
你有的是第一种女朋友
it's the first kind of girlfriend.
你做的马卡龙怎么样?
How are your macaroons?
呃... 哦 唔
Uh...oh. Mm.
我的马卡龙?
My macaroons?
棒极了
Great.
只要一小口 就仿若置身法国天堂
A little bit of French heaven.
你叫什么?
What is your name?
我叫Max
Max.
这么拼M-a-x
M-a-x.
每个字都如雷贯耳
Nothing is silent. Ever.
我懂了
So I gather.
好了 你去填写申请表吧 Max
Okay. Why don't you go fill out an application, Max.
扣子可以扣上了
And you can put those away again.
我不怎么爱大波妹的
I'm really not into big-breasted women.
搞定了
Girl, you got this.
第一天上班紧张吗 老妹儿?
First day. Are you nervous, girl?
拜托 在你的三个哥哥都出柜了之后
Please. Nervous is telling your elderly Mormon parents
还得告诉年迈的爹妈说自己也是同性恋
that you're gay after your three older siblings
那才叫紧张呢
already came out.
我都不知道这些甜品都是啥玩意
I have no idea what most of these desserts are.
自"迷失"剧终后 我从未感到如此迷失了
I haven't felt this lost since the finale of Lost.
Max 我身上还有挂着巴尼百货的标价牌吗?
Max, can you see any of the Barney's price tags on these?
哦 你的裤子里面好像
Uh, I think there's one bunching up
有个标签支出来了
inside the back of your pants.
那是内裤的标签 我得还回去的
No, that's the underwear I'm also returning.
她来了
Here she comes.
嗨 姑娘们 这是Naomi
Hi, ladies. This is Naomi,
甜点餐台的迎宾小姐
the dessert bar hostess.
走啊 Naomi 走
Go, Naomi, go.
人长得好看 但就跟时下的新偶像一样傻
Gorgeous, but as dumb as whoever is the hot new idiot right now.
让我看一下你们
Let me take a look at you.
走吧
Good-bye.
这就不要我了?
Already?
珍珠项链 快扔掉
Those pearls. They have to go.
为什么啊?
Really? It's just, well,
它们对我来说有特殊意义的
I'm kind of emotionally attached to them.
亲 我爱我的法国斗牛犬
Well, honey, I love my half-blind French bulldog,
但我可不把它挂在脖子上
but I don't wear her around my neck.
Max 让我看一下
Max, let me take a look.
很好
Love it.
大方得体 很赞
Fabulous. Well done.
嗨 Joe 新店开张 我太兴奋了
Hi, Joe. Big day. I'm so excited.
你可以进去一个人偷着乐吗?
Why don't you be excited in the back, doll?
我想让Max站在前台
I want Max up front now.
人们一直在对我说别出柜
All my life, people have been telling me not to come out.
看来这里的也不希望我出啊?
Why should here be any different?
姑娘们 我刚听说纽约时报的美食评论家
Ladies, I just got word that the New York Times food critic
今天下午会突然造访
may make a surprise visit this afternoon.
我们要尽善尽美...
Everything has to be perfect...
服务周到 甜点美味
the service, the desserts,
还有我脆弱的小神经
the precarious balance of my meds.
不能出一丝差错
Nothing can go wrong.
Naomi啊
Naomi.
快去接待
Fetch.
"欢迎来到'糕潮'餐厅"
"Welcome to The High"
"嗨 欢迎来到'糕潮'餐厅"
"Hi. Welcome to The High""
"欢迎来到'糕潮'餐厅"
"Welcome to The High"
别再说"糕潮"了 我现在一点也不兴奋
Stop saying high. It reminds me I'm not.
等等 Max 你不兴奋?
Wait, Max, you're not high?
一点都没?
Like, not high at all?
没有 我可不想把事情搞砸
No. I didn't want to screw today up.
你到底是怎么回事啊?
What the hell is wrong with you?
你今天怎么也得撑下去
You can't change who you are today.
纽约时报要来了
The New York Times is coming.
你怎么应对?
How will you cope?
你上一次不兴奋是在啥时候了?
I mean, when's the last time you weren't high?
我出生的时候
My birth.
但我喝高了
But I was really drunk.
喝了一大瓶白酒
I had just had a bottle of wine.
其实是我妈喝的
Well, my mother had.
我得去招呼客人了
I have to go wait on those customers.
你要使出全力
Do what you can to get with the program.
我是说 你赶紧兴奋起来
I mean, get off the program.
不吸上几口 不能搞烘焙
You can't bake not baked.
大玛丽?
Big Mary?
John 在哪?
John?
你怎么不叫我的新名字?
Why not try my new name?
卡西莫多
Quasimodo.
"巴黎圣母院"里的驼背敲钟人 总是躲在暗处
你有大麻吗?
Do you have any weed?
我有大麻吗?
Do I have any weed?
我到自己的驼背里那里找找
Let me check my hump.
没有大麻
Nope. No weed.
谢谢 Rico 因为严禁种族歧视
Thanks, Rico. I didn't want to ask
我本来都不打算问你要的
due to the city-wide ban on racial profiling.
哇 这个储物间比新泽西州长
Wow. This dish room is cleaner
克里斯·克里斯蒂的盘子还干净
than Chris Christie's plate after lunch.
Max 我需要两份薰衣草杏仁饼干
Max, I need two lavender macaroons.
- 哪里有?  - 我这就准备
- Where are they?  - I'm working on them.
很好 真为你骄傲
Well, good. I'm so proud of you.
这简直是"辣妈辣妹"的情景再现
This is so Freaky Friday.
薰衣草杏仁饼干来了
Here are the lavender macaroons.
看到没? 就连端盘子我都比你厉害
See? Even just holding this, I'm better.
希望一切都顺顺利利
Now we just have to hope nothing goes wrong.
惊喜来了!
Surprise!
我们都来给你们捧场了
We all came to support you.
好吧
Well, that's it.
纽约时报的美食评论家有可能
The New York Times food critic may be in the same room
会和Han Earl Oleg 还有Sophie坐在一起
as Han, Earl, Oleg, and Sophie.
我们死定了 死于11点30分
We're dead. Time of death, 11:30.
我在4点20分就死了
I believe it's more like 4:20.
哦 Caroline 我喜欢这地方
Oh, Caroline, I love your new place.
看起来清新亮丽
It's so fresh and pretty.
就像那些傻逼广告
It kind of looks like a douche commercial.
说的没错 亲爱的
You're right, baby.
确实很像那些傻逼广告
It looks exactly like a douche commercial.
好了 能不能不要在高级甜品店
Okay. Can we stop saying "Douche"
说"傻逼"这个词?
in the fancy pastry shop?
我同意 太不合适了
I agree. Not appropriate.
亲爱的Caroline 请把我的电话号码
Caroline, darling, slip my phone number
给那边的努比亚美女
to that fine Nubian princess.
并转告她 不要被我的老屁股给迷惑了
And tell her not to be fooled by my bad hip.
我会带她嗨翻世界
I can still gently rock her world.
好吧 你们来这里是干嘛呢
Okay, guys, what are you doing here
能不能快点离开?
and how quickly can you leave?
太好了
Real nice.
我们大老远过来
After we came all this way
只想尝尝Max
to just order only desserts
独家烹饪的甜点
that Max knows how to make
感受你周到热情的服务
and to say nice things about you as a waitress.
哦 你们是为了我?
Oh, you'd do that for me?
当然不是 我演不下去了
Hell no, I can't pull that off.
如果我会演戏 我早就卖了餐厅
If I could act, I'd sell the restaurant
接演有线电视节目的
and get cast in two-line roles as the doctor
那些医生角色
on any network television show.
Sophie是真正的演员
Sophie's the actress.
而且她很有一套
And trust me, she's got quite a repertoire.
我称她为床上奥斯卡演后
In bed, I call her Meryl Sheets.
来一个 亲爱的
Do it, baby.
哦 这地方真不错
Oh, what a lovely place.
她这口音就是在我们扮演
That's the accent she uses when we play
"为性奴十二年"用的
"12 Years A Sex Slave."
帅哥美女们 我马上回来
Lovely, be right back.
对了 欢迎光临"糕潮"
Oh, and, welcome to The High.
那张桌是怎么回事?
What's going on with that table?
那是镇上的欧洲马戏团吗?
Is there a European circus in town?
马戏团? 我不清楚
A circus? Well, I wouldn't know.
我完全不知道他们是谁
I really have no idea who they are.
那不是在问你话
That didn't require an answer.
而是我准确无误的观察结果
It was just one of my dead-on observations.
把他们打发走吧
Just get rid of them.
就说 我们的漏斗蛋糕卖完了
Tell them we've run out of funnel cakes.
我感觉找回自己了
Well, I'm feeling like my old self.
Joe刚刚让我把他们打发走
Joe just told me to lose Han, Earl, Oleg, and Sophie.
我要怎么弄走那么多人?
How am I supposed to lose that many people?
我又不是航空管制员
I'm not air traffic control.
你表现得像是他们不懂得在高档场合
You are acting like they don't know how to act
该如何言行
in a fancy place.
姑娘们 看啊!
Girls, look!
Oleg把餐巾纸当作派对帽那样来戴
Oleg's wearing his napkin as a party hat.
你的甜品 祝你胃口大开
Here's your dessert. Bon appetite.
Max 我不敢相信你做到了
Max, I can't believe you just made that.
我也不敢相信
Neither can I.
你跟Oleg和Sophie说什么了?
And what did you say to Oleg and Sophie?
已经一小时了 我都没看到
It's been an hour, and I haven't seen
任何不雅的举动
any over-the-table penetration.
我只是告诉他们 拿出最好的礼仪来
I just told them to be on their best behavior,
然后他们就没事了
and they're fine with it.
打扰一下 Max
Excuse me, Max.
对 你好
Yes, hi.
我能去尿尿吗?
May I go tinkle?
还是说 这违反了监狱甜品区的规矩?
Or is that against the law here at Guantanamo Dessert Bay?
我要去女厕所做爱
I'm gonna go have sex in the ladies room.
除非你们这两个假正经的人也反对这事
Unless you two prudes have a problem with that, too.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
能给我一杯拿铁和一杯红酒吗?
Can I get a latte and a red wine?
因为有片止痛药堵在我喉咙里了
'Cause I got a Vicodin stuck in my throat.
天啊
Oh, my God.
大中午的有谁能够
Who could be that messed up
这么狼狈不堪?
in the middle of the afternoon?
呃 我的新闺蜜
Uh, my new best friend.
我最好必须在Joe或者是
I better get rid of her before Joe
时报评论员进来前 把她撵走
or that Times critic walks in.
你继续偶然地创造出美食吧
You keep doing good things by accident.
你好 我能不能...
Hi, can I get a...
当然可以 但不是在这里
You sure can. Anywhere but here.
哦 不 现在我不能转圈圈
Oh, no. Spinning's not good for me right now.
她在这儿干什么?
What is she doing here?
马上离开 你就当没看见过她
Leaving. You never saw her.
- 等等  - Joe 我来搞定
- Wait.  - Joe, I got this.
我在学校的闺蜜曾经对
My bestie at school was totally hooked
处方药相当上瘾 持续差不多一周
on prescription pills for, like, a week.
嘿 你好啊
Hey, hi, you.
你好 请问Max在哪里?
Excuse me. Where is Max?
她去后厨一下下
She's in the back for a sec.
看来...
So...
我们又见面了
We meet again.
先生 你找后厨的人有事吗?
Sir, do you need something in the back?
是的 Caroline说她会给我一张餐巾纸
Yes, Caroline said she'd bring me a napkin,
但是我直接打电话给华纳都比她来得要快
but I could get Time Warner on the phone faster than that.
去问Max啊
Just ask Max.
她一直在餐厅替Caroline打掩护
She covers for Caroline all the time at the diner.
Max 是吗?
Max?
噢 有好戏看了
Ooh. Drama at The High.
Han 那是我的新老板
Han, that's my new boss.
别再说了
Stop talking.
还有 别再收集贴纸了 你是大人了
Also, stop collecting stickers. You're a grown-up.
好了 我把那个药瘾女赶走了
Okay, I threw that drug addict out.
那个药瘾女是我的女朋友
That drug addict is my girlfriend.
更多好戏在后头
More drama at The High.
Caroline 我有事情跟你说
And Caroline, we have a problem.
你管Allie叫药瘾女
You called Allie a drug addict.
哦 那是她的名字吗?
Oh, is that her name?
Allie? 真可爱
Allie? So cute.
还很美
Even lovelier.
刚那个小不点说
And according to that very small man,
你还是个糟糕的服务员
you're also a terrible waitress.
我都不知道你们俩在一起
But I had no idea you two were together.
我还以为是更有力的...
I would have thought a powerful...
打住 现在
Stop. Now.
Joe 我们真的很需要这些工作
Joe, look, we really need these jobs.
我们在糕点生意上做了错误的决定
We made a bad decision with our bakery business,
导致我们无法偿还巨额的银行贷款
and we have a big bank loan that we can't pay.
很诚实 不错
Honesty. Good.
大家都会被诚实打动
People respond to honesty.
虽然我不会 但他们会
I don't, but they do.
Max 你在这一行具有潜力
Max, you have potential here.
Caroline 作为服务员 你被炒了
Caroline, you're fired as a waitress.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
打住!
Stop!
那里面没什么能救你的
There's nothing in there to save you.
好吧 要是她被炒 那我也被炒了
Well, if she's fired, I'm fired, too.
哦 别冲动 诺玛·蕾
Oh, relax, Norma Rae.
诺玛·蕾：反抗资本家剥削的工人
作为服务员 她被炒了
She's fired as a waitress,
但我会雇佣她当迎宾小姐
but she's hired as a hostess.
真的吗? 为什么?
I am? Why?
因为你很漂亮 又亮出了胸部
Because you're pretty, you flashed a boob,
而且比起Allie呆过的三家戒瘾中心
and you took more control of Allie in five minutes
你能在五分钟就把她给控制住了
than anybody's been able to do in her three rehab stints.
简直就是纽约的救星了
And that, lady, is a New York City hostess.
姑娘们 我被轰出来了
Well, girls, I struck out.
比尔·科斯比毁了所有超过七十岁的
Bill Cosby has ruined it for all black men over 70
比尔·科斯比(美国黑人演员)曾被爆强奸夜总会女郎
纯粹想给小姑娘买杯酒的黑种男人
who are just trying to buy a gal a drink.
Max 你能相信吗?
Max, how do you like that?
我是迎宾小姐了 我升职了!
I'm the hostess. I got a promotion!
我不觉得迎宾小姐是升职...
I don't think a hostess is a promo...
是的 Max 因为我们的银行余额是负数
It is, Max, 'cause with a less-than-zero bank balance,
所以这就是升职 我仅有的希望了
it has to be. It's all I have left.